As we all travel across the sea,
raising our voices, we take
in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to
go, everybody rejoices.
Now let's go, get the sails all unfurled.
La la la la la.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure,
we're itching to try.
Get ready to roam.
So all aboard now we're said to go!
Set sail to the ocean so deep.
Ready for a truly grand adventure!
Well don't you think
that sounds really fun?
All this excitement is second to none.
As we all travel across the
sea, Raising our voices we take!
In the beautiful blue world,
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices!
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled.
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget,
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set.
Now I won't be scared!
As long as I keep that feeling there.
With that, let us keep up the pace!
While enjoying every
trip from place to place.
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained.
So let's keep going, adventure awaits!
So many treasures await!
So now let's raise our voices in pride!
Laughing out when they are found!
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices!
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud!
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous.
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
I took off my pants.
I hope no one saw me.
It's scary outside but
I'm still having fun.
All alone but I'm still having fun.
Hello.
25 degrees!
Quick, somebody look!
Oh wait, I'm the only one here!
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Come on, Quark! Wake up!
Get with the program already!
Yeah, pal, look!
We started an island!
It's a summer island!
Check out the beach!
Uh, wait, are you?
I mean, is this?
Is this real? You're alive!
Hurry up, Brooke! What's wrong?
Yeah, we can't get this
thing started without you!
Everyone's here!
Ow!
I'm happy, but... Ow!
You mean you didn't die after all?
What happened?
You were having a bad dream, that's all.
Now get over here and play a song.
Ah!
I can't believe it. That really hurt.
That means this isn't a
dream, this is reality!
It was just a nightmare
after all, thank goodness!
I hope Captain York made
it to the comm belt.
You think he'll be okay?
That's a question for the waves.
All we can do is carry
out his final orders.
We'll sail around the world
until we see Laboon again.
Rise and shine.
Do you have to do this every day?
The winds are too strong.
The sail's gonna turn.
This is nothing.
We'll sing our way through.
Wow, look at this, Brooke.
You got yourself a bounty. Nice job.
Hey, what's the problem, Brooke?
Why'd you stop to jam it? Keep going!
I've been jumping to my nose for this!
Give me a moment, please.
Let's see.
I didn't know you could do that!
This is a tone dial.
I purchased it from a
merchant ship many years ago.
I hear there are many
different kinds of dials,
but this one in particular has the
ability to record and reproduce sounds.
Oh, we saw those in Skypiea.
Then you know how they work.
You see,
when I meet Laboon again, I
want to play this for him,
so it's something I
always keep in my heart.
So do you have something
special recorded on it?
Yes, a song.
It's the last song
performed by my former crew.
Although they're all gone now,
we wanted to leave a
message to Laboon to let
him know that we were
merry until the bitter end.
May I play it for you now?
Ooh, yeah, do it!
If Laboon will like it, I bet I will, too!
All right.
Are there any survivors?
Surely a few of us can still stand.
We got a couple men left,
but I don't think there's much
hope left for us at this point.
Well, at least we're all
dying together, right?
I guess their weapons
were all poison-tipped.
And our doctor's dead now, too.
When I became a pirate, I knew I might
die on the seas, and I was ready for that.
But I still have just one regret.
Laboon.
Hey, Brooke, how does that devil
fruit of yours work? Who knows?
This is my first time dying.
But wait I have an idea If
we're going to die anyway
Why don't we sing a song
I don't know what will happen Any
more than you do But if the revive
revive fruit Really does bring me
back to life After I die here I will
deliver this to him without fail
The tone dial I'll take Laboon the
song He and our captain love The
song we've all shared so many times
and when we meet at that cape
he'll Know this crew died without
regrets that we kept our promise to
our dear Friend that's a great idea
all right men don't you dare die
until we finish this Song this is it
the rum bar pirates once-in-a-lifetime
performance for our our friend,
across the seas.
Huh?
If this is the song you're
playing, we can all sing along!
Yeah!
Yo-ho, yo-ho,
yo-ho,
yo-ho, yo-ho,
yo-ho, yo-ho.
Gather up all of the crew.
It's time to ship up Aix's brew.
Sea wind blows to air.
Who knows the waves will be our guide?
Or across the ocean's tide?
Rays of sunshine far and wide!
Birds they sing of cheerful things!
In circles passing by!
Bid farewell to Weaver's town!
Say so long to Port Renown!
Sing a song, it won't be long!
Before we're casting off!
Across the gold and silver seas!
A salty spray puts us at ease!
Day and night to our delight!
The voyage never rests!
Gather up all of the crew, it's
time to ship out Binx's crew!
Pirates, we eternally are
challenging the scene!
With the waves to rest our heads,
ship beneath us as our beds!
Hoisted high upon the mast,
our jolly Roger flies!
Somewhere in the endless skies,
stormy winds are blowing like!
Waves are dancing, evening comes,
it's time to sound the drums!
But steady men and never fear,
tomorrow's skies are always clear!
So pound your feet and clap your
hands till sunny days return!
Yo-ho-ho-ho,
Gather up all of the crew!
It's time to ship out Binx's brew!
Wave goodbye but don't you cry!
Our memories remain!
Our days are but a passing dream!
Everlasting though they seem!
Neat the moon we'll meet again!
The winds of the lullaby!
Gather up all of the crew!
It's time to ship out Binx's brew!
Sing a song and play along!
For all the ocean's wild!
After all is said and done!
You'll end up a skeleton!
So spread your tail from dawn!
Till dusk upon each holy seas!
Yo-ho-ho,
Well, it would seem
we're down to a quartet.
A trio.
And a duet.
A solo
It isn't right Leaving
just the accompaniment
If you want to join my crew All
I ask is that you love music
Let's hear it for the Rumbar Pirates The
crew that brings a smile to every child
The moon Once we travel the world
we're coming right back here
You just wait for us
Thank
you.
Laboon, thank you for waiting for us.
I know that 50 years is
a long time, but please,
do you think you could be
patient for one or two more?
I have my pride as a pirate.
I promised you I would see you
again after circling the globe.
I intend to keep my word and
return from the right direction.
Hey, Skeleton!
You ain't singing anymore?
One more song!
Come on!
When this was recorded, my comrades
and I knew the end was near.
But we sang our hearts out, because this
would be the Rumbar Pirate Swan song.
For over 50 years, I sailed alone,
drifting aimlessly in that dark, misty sea.
Hearing this song was my only comfort.
All alone on that giant ship,
this made me feel human.
In that sad and lonely place, it
was my only link to other people.
But now.
I will proceed with a new strength.
And I can seal this tone dial away.
Until it can finally fulfill
its original purpose. Goodbye.
He did that weird head thing again.
I'm glad to hear that Laboon is
well and still waiting for me.
My shadow has returned.
and we're leaving the Devil's Sea.
And although the voices in this
dial kept me sane all those years,
I must remember that
it was not for my sake?
that they were first recorded.
This is a song for Laboon
to remember his old friends.
Every day on that boat was difficult
and there was no end in sight.
Frankly, I'd given up all hope.
I'm so good.
I'm so glad to still be alive!
I'm so glad I never gave up,
no matter how hard it was.
Well, of course, right?
I've waited so long for this day to come.
So, does the offer to join
your crew still stand?
Yeah, welcome aboard!
Wado!
Just like that!
But good to have you!
We finally got our musician!
He may be all bones, but
he sure knows how to play!
I've been wanting a
musician since forever!
He had a heavy heart, but
he's light as a father!
By the way, what do you
call a singing skeleton?
Yeah, tell us, Brooke!
A natural bone singer!
Bones, get him, it's funny, because,
you know, get him, it's funny.
Yeah, I got him.
The crew certainly is likely now, huh?
Why do we always have to
attract those types? So noisy.
I don't know what's going on,
but congratulations, Namizo.
Uh, thanks, I guess.
I don't know what's going on, but cheers!
I'm confused too, but cheers!
45 degrees!
I won't turn back.
Not after coming so far.
I may have been sidetracked for a while.
But I'm headed straight forward again.
All the way around the world.
Back to Twin Cape.
So far away.
Because I know you'll be waiting for me.
And I have to keep my promise.
Both to you and my crew.
So I will see this to the end.
No matter what.
So wait for me.
Just a little bit longer.
Hey, Le Boon, what's wrong?
Well, you seem to be
in high spirits today.
I wonder why.
Take a look at this a wanted poster you
mean you already have a bounty on you
Pardon me for not introducing myself properly
before I am known as Dead Bones Brook
And I'm a wanted man my nickname
is the humming swordsman
I have a bounty of 33 million
berries On my head I was the
leader of a battle convoy in the
kingdom of my origin afterwards
I served As a musician and
swordsman in the rumbar pirates
later succeeding yorkie as
captain of the crew Until their
demise but now I pledge my
life and my services to Captain
Monkey D Luffy of the Straw Hat
Pirates I shall do my best to
make you proud that is to say
I shall work myself to the bone
All right!
One more toast!
Raise your glasses!
How splendid.
Thank you, Franky Usopp.
It's perfect.
No problem, bro.
I can make one of these
any day of the week.
But it was my design, just so you know.
Yeah, but I picked out the flowers.
But truly, it's a beautiful memorial.
And this is certainly for the best,
since I could scarcely bring
all of those bones onto Mr.
Lion with me.
Okay, but it's Thousand
Sunny, not Mr. Lion.
You know, by happy coincidence?
Thriller Bark originally
came from the West Blue.
just like the Rumbar Pirates.
Despite the troubles this ship brought me,
I hope my friends will rest peacefully
in the soil of their homeland.
We're gonna head back now Brooke.
We'll see you soon.
Glad you like it. Bye-bye.
Thank you
Goodness,
you gave me a fright You were out for
quite a while, are you feeling better?
Yeah, I overslept a bit
And what is that?
A dead sword, Yubashiri.
I'm laying it to rest here, too.
Muffy is the man who
become king of the pirates!
Um, what is it?
No.
Nothing.
Oh, in case you hadn't heard,
I officially joined the crew.
I see.
Well, that's too bad for
you now, isn't it? Huh?
This crew can be a real
handful, that's all.
So it would seem.
But I'll give them my blood
and sweat all the same,
except I don't have any
since I'm a skeleton.
Zorro's up, so on to our next adventure!
Come on, it's time to set sail!
Yeah!
Hey!
Zoro, you took off your bandages!
Of course I did.
They made it hard to move.
That's the point!
You're supposed to sit still in a hill!
Come here!
Setting off already?
I'm sorry you can't stick around.
Whenever you feel like leaving,
you can take Brooke's ship.
I fixed the rudder and the sails for you.
It's wonderful.
I can't thank you enough
for all you've done.
It might take the rest of my life for me
to pay you back, but I'm willing to try.
In other words, what do you
say you and I get married?
Sorry, babe, you're a champ,
but it won't work out.
I'm afraid I'm just too
super to settle down.
I really hate to see you take off.
You sure you don't want to stick
around and party for a few more days?
No way!
We're off to Fishman Island, and
it's going to be totally awesome!
Fish dudes!
There's going to be fish dudes!
Screw the fish dudes!
There are going to be mermaids!
I'm going to flirt with all of them!
I wonder if the mermaids
we encounter would
be so gracious as to
show me their panties.
Hey, man, don't be dumb!
Think about what you're saying!
Mermaids don't wear any panties.
And I'm telling you,
mermaids are so gorgeous,
they even give the pirate empress
Hancock a run for her money.
Mermaids, yeah!
Mermaids are fish from the waist down.
Why do you guys know so
much about Fishman Island?
Ah, well, a couple years back before
we got stuck in this hellhole,
we took a trip there.
You were gonna love it.
Wow, Lola, I didn't realize you
went to the New World already.
We didn't go there, you big silly.
We came from there in the first place.
My mama's a pirate just like me, you know?
Oh, that reminds me.
Here, you should take this.
It's my mama's Viva card.
A piece of paper?
Whoa, hang on to that one.
One of the greatest pirates
I've ever met in my life.
This is Lola's mom.
That'll come in handy someday.
Not just anybody gets one of those.
Sorry, but what's a Viva card again?
What?
You guys don't know?
Come on, Captain, don't be insensitive.
They only make Viva
cards in the new world.
Oh, I forgot about that.
Anyway, this is no normal paper.
You can wet it or burn
it, but it won't change.
If you take a piece of your fingernail
to the shop where they make these,
they'll use it to create a personalized
piece of paper, just like this one.
Because of their use, they also call
Viva cards life paper sometimes.
The idea is to tear off
a piece and give it to
your family or friends
when you go on a journey.
Uh-huh. And then what?
Take a look.
This is the Viva card I got for my mama.
Oh, it's moving!
No matter where in the world these scraps
of paper are, they're drawn to each other.
So long as I have this, I know
what direction mama is in.
It doesn't tell you the
distance, though, I'm afraid.
Whoa, that's so neat!
I bet there's a bunch of crazy stuff
like that in the new world, huh?
Well, I don't know about crazy,
but it certainly is handy.
Anyway, I'm signing the piece of my mama's
Viva card, so if you're ever in trouble,
you can use it to find her
and she'll help you out.
If that ever happens, be sure to
tell her that I'm doing fine, okay?
Wow, thanks, Lola.
Hey, hold on.
Don't I have one of those already?
Huh?
I almost forgot, but Ace gave you
something like this a long time ago.
You remember that, right?
That scrap of paper
will reunite us someday.
So that's what it was.
This is it, but...
Huh, that's weird.
I thought you said these
things couldn't burn.
Are you kidding?
Let me see that!
This is definitely a Viva card,
but there's something I
neglected to tell you before.
The life force of the owner is
also reflected on the paper.
Does this belong to someone close to you?
Yeah, it's my big brother's.
Lola?
I'm sorry to say this, but your brother's
life is in terrible danger right now.